Guide to the National Lawyers Guild Records TAM.191
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Part 1, Series VIII: Publications, 1941-1967
  - New York Guild Lawyer, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - New York Guild Lawyer: Correspondence, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - New York Guild Lawyer: Editorial Board, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - New York Guild Lawyer: Review Copies, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Lawyers Guild Review: Reports of Publication, 1954-1959 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - National Guild Review, 1955 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - New York Guild Lawyer Ads, 1955 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - New York Guild Lawyer: Correspondence, 1955 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - New York Guild Lawyer: Editorial Board, 1955 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - New York Guild Lawyer: Review Copies, 1955 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Civil Liberties Docket: ACLU, 1955-1956 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Civil Liberties Docket: ACLU, 1955-1956 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Civil Liberties Docket: ACLU, 1955-1956 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Civil Liberties Docket: ACLU, 1955-1956 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Civil Liberties Docket: Publicity, 1955-1956 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Civil Liberties Docket, 1955-1957 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Civil Liberties Docket: Subscriptions, 1955-1957 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Lawyers Guild Review: Correspondence, 1955-1957 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Civil Liberties Docket: Correspondence [I], 1956 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Civil Liberties Docket: Correspondence [II], 1956 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Civil Liberties Docket: Publication, 1956 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Lawyers Guild Review, 1956 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Lawyers Guild Review, 1956 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Lawyers Guild Review, 1956-1957 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Lawyers Guild Review: Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Lawyers Guild Review: Ads, 1956-1957 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Requests for Publication, 1956-1957 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Civil Liberties Docket: Court Clerk Inquiries, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Lawyers Guild Review: Agency Accounts, 1957-1958 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Lawyers Guild Review: Cancellations, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Lawyers Guild Review: Draft, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Lawyers Guild Review: Fall Issue, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Lawyers Guild Review: Subscriptions, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Lawyers Guild Review: Winter Issue, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - New York Guild Lawyer, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Lawyers Guild Review: Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Lawyers Guild Review: Special Issue, 1957-1958 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Lawyers Guild Review: Announcements, Mailing Lists, 1958 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Lawyers Guild Review: Orders for Integration Issue, 1958 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Lawyers Guild Review: Summer Issue, 1958 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Lawyers Guild Review: Correspondence, 1958-1960 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Guild Lawyer Publication Articles, 1959, 1962, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Civil Liberties Docket, 1959-1963 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Lawyers Guild Review: Correspondence, 1960-1964 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Guild Lawyer Article, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Guild Lawyer Correspondence, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Lawyers Guild Review: Law in Transition, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Lawyers Guild Review: Law in Transition, 1961-1962 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - The Guild Lawyer: Survey, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - The Guild Lawyer, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Subscribers: Referral Directory, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Lawyers Guild Review: Style Sheet, Undated (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Part 1, Series IX: Dinners, Events and Conferences, 1937-1978
  - Convention and Seminar Programs, 1937-1978 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Conference on Administrative Law, 1939 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Conference on Contemporary Problems in Labor Law & Relations, 1940 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Labor Law Conference, 1940 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Dinner Address by Judge J. Warren Madden, 1941 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Lecture Series, 1941 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Theatre Party, 1941 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Transit Conference, 1941 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Banquet: War Convention, 1943 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Somervell Dinner, 1943 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Somervell Dinner, 1943-1944 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Conference on Reconversion, 1944 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - National Wartime Conference for Professionals, 1944 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Robert F. Wagner Dinner, 1944 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - National Emergency Conference, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - World Security Conference: San Francisco, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Far Western Conference, 1947 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Labor Conference, 1947 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - National Convention on International Law, 1947 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Luncheon: Judge J. Waties Waring, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Theatre Party: Double Bill, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Theatre Party: Double Bill, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Lecture Series, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Legislative Conference [I], 1950 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Legislative Conference [II], 1950 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Legislative Conference: Material Issues, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Conference: Civil Liberties [I], 1951 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Conference: Civil Liberties [II], 1951 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Luncheon: Hallinan, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Theatre Parties, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Theatre Party: Guys and Dolls, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Theatre Party: The Rose Tattoo, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Civil Liberties Panel, 1951-1952 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Buffet Supper, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Civil Rights Conference, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Civil Rights Conference, 1952-1953 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Contributions to Frank Serri Reception, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Concert/Guild Revue, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Fundraising: Guild Revue, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Lecture: Preparation of Real Estate Sales Contracts, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Legislative Conference, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - National Conference re: Civil Rights, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Theatre Parties: Cleopatra Plays, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Conference, 1953 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Conference: Independence of the Bar, 1953 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Conference on Threats to Independence of the Bar, 1953 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Denial of Willkie Memorial, 1953 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Theatre Party: Town Hall, 1953 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Theatre Party Town Hall Concert, 1953 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Theatre Party: Variety Concert, 1953 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Banquet at Commodore Hotel, 1954 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Dinner Meeting, 1954 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Emergency Dinner, 1954 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Banquet, 1954 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Letters Inviting Main Speaker to Banquet- NYC (contains letter from Albert Einstein), 1954 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Banquet Committee, 1955 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Civil Liberties Conference, 1955 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Conference: Invite, 1955 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Robert Silberstein Dinner, 1955 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Legislative Conference on Rent Control [I], 1955 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Legislative Conference on Rent Control [II], 1955 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Theatre Party: Bus Stop, 1955 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Theatre Party: Bus Stop(Music Box Theater Plan), 1955 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Theatre Party: A Month in the Country, 1956 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Ticket Orders: A Month in the Country, 1956 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Theatre Party: Separate Tables, 1956 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Theatre Party: Separate Tables Order Forms, 1956 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Linder dinner, 1956-1957 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Panel on Due Process, 1956-1957 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Theater Parties: General Information, 1956-1957 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Banquet: New York City, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Banquet: Checklists/ Schedules, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Banquet: Contract/Seating Plan, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Banquet: Guild Members' Biographies, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Banquet: Hotel Correspondence- Reports, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Banquet: Invitations and Program, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Banquet: Printer, Letter shop, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Civil Liberties Conference [I], 1957 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Civil Liberties Conference [II], 1957 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Invitations to Civil Liberties Conference, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Theatre Party: Tunnel of Love, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Theatre Party: Tunnel of Love Correspondence, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Bills: David L. Weissman Dinner, 1958 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Meeting: Integration in Housing, 1958 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Theatre Party: Moiseyev Dancers, 1958 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Banquet: Honoring Osmond Fraenkel, 1958-1959 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Banquet: Replies to Invitations, 1959 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Conference on Law Reform, 1959 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Theatre Party: Bolshoi Ballet, 1959 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Theatre Party: The Gangs All Here, 1959 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - NLG Theatre Parties, 1959-1960 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - News of the Theatre/ Leonard Wacker Agreement, 1959-1960 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Victor Rabinowitz Dinner, 1959-1960 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Labor Law Conference: Correspondence, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Labor Law Conference:General Information, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Conference: Information Kit, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - House Party: Phillip and Bea Jones, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - House Party: Quat-Faulkner Party, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - House Party: Rothenberg, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - International Law Conference, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Civil Rights and Civil Liberties Panels, 1961-1962 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - North-South Conference, 1961-1962 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Congressional Dinner: Program, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Atlanta Conference, 1962 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Atlanta Conference On Negligence and Civil Rights Law, 1962 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Banquet: Procedures, 1962 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Civil Rights Workshop, 1962 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Forum on Narcotics, 1962-1964 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Luncheon Award to Southern Lawyers, 1962 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Silver Anniversary Banquet, 1962 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Southern Conference Educational Fund, 1962-1963 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - SNCC Conference, 1962 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - Chicago Civil Rights Conference, 1963 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - New Orleans Civil Rights Conference, 1963 (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Washington, D.C. Civil Rights Conference, 1963 (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - Jan Dinner, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - Orientation Conference, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Seminars and Conferences, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - Drawing Boards Conference: Chicago, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - Midwest Conference on Cops, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - Radical Professions: Ann Arbor, Michigan, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 39)
  - Lawyers Draft Referral Panel, 1967-1968 (Box 30, Folder 40)
  - Conference "Legal Aspects of the Draft", 1968 (Box 30, Folder 41)
  - Military Law Conference, NYU, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 42)
  - NLG Dinner to Honor Morton and Helen Sobell and Reies Lopez Tijerina, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 43)
  - Banquet: Expense, Receipts, Undated (Box 30, Folder 44)
  - Conference: Vocations for Radicals, Paper Tiger, Undated (Box 30, Folder 45)
  - Election Law Seminar, Undated (Box 30, Folder 46)
  - Fund Raising Lists, Undated (Box 30, Folder 47)
- Part 1, Series X: Political Issues, Including Government Investigations, 1942-1968
  - Review and Analysis of the Dies Committee, 1942 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Dies Committee in Opposition to Cox Resolution, 1943 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Civil Liberties: House Un-American Committee and Loyalty Program, 1947 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Civil Liberties: Loyalty Procedures, 1947-1948 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Un-American Activities: John T. McTernan, 1948 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Judiciary/Appointment of Judges, 1949 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - National Committee, 1949 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - FBI Report: Sacher, 1949 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Subversive Activities Bills: Statement Chafee, 1949-1950 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Congressional Investigation Committee, 1952-1955 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Brownell Action [I], 1953 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Brownell Action [II], 1953 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Extracts from Addresses by Attorney General, 1953 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Reports from Various Committees; New York State Assembly and Senate, 1953 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Administration Proceedings re: Brownell, 1953-1954 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Government Listing of Un-American Activities, 1953-1954 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Congressional Discussion of Guild as Subversive, 1954 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Civil Liberties (Hennings Subcommittee), 1955-1956 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Hearings Before Committee on Un-American Activities, 1955 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Internal Security Act: Harry Sacher, 1955 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Judiciary Committee Congressional, 1955 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - 84th Congress, 2nd Session: Acts, Bills, Resolutions, 1956 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Answer to Statement of Grounds, 1956 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Application for Eliminating Interrogations, 1956 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Bills to Overcome Nelson Case, 1956-1957 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Eastland Committee Report, 1956 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Coddaire Ruling: re: Executive Order 10450, 1957 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Congressional Investigation Committee, 1957-1958 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Supplemental Memorandum/Attorney General's Answer, 1957 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: From Congress (re: House Committee on Un-American Activities), 1959 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: re: Un-American Activities Committee, 1959 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - House Un-American Activities Committee: Congress Bills, 1959 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - House Un-Americans Committee, 1961 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Repeal: Law Creating East Hudson Authority, 1961 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Civil Rights Legal Papers, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - American Foreign Policy and Rule of Law, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Report and Correspondence: Housing, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Papers re: FBI and Individual Rights, Undated (Box 32, Folder 20)
- Part 1, Series XI: Legislation, 1936-1961
  - 13th, 14th and 15th Amendments, 1949-1950 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - 14th Amendment Section II, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Anti-Bills and Legislation, 1945 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Bar Committee Against Test Oaths (CA Senate Bill # 298), 1949 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Brydges Becker Bill, 1951 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Civil Rights Legislation, 1956 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Communist Party Bills, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Expatriation Bill Report, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - Federal Jurors, 1948-1952 (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - Forand Bill, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - Habeas Corpus Legislation, 1958 (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - Hobbs Bill, 1943 (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - Housing and Rent Act, 1947-1949 (Box 32, Folder 33)
  - Legislation: HR 9352, Undated (Box 32, Folder 34)
  - Legislation: HR 9937 Internal Security, 1957-1958 (Box 32, Folder 35)
  - Internal Security Legislation, 1957-1958 (Box 32, Folder 36)
  - Jenner Bill- Butler Amendments, 1958 (Box 32, Folder 37)
  - Kennedy- McCarthy Federal Unemployment Act of 1958 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Labor: Model Labor Relations Acts, Anti-Detective Agencies, 1937 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Legal Status of Women Legislation, 1950 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Legislative Activity, 1956 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Legislative Activity: Analyses of Bills, Clippings, 1956 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Legislative Activity: Correspondence, 1956 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Legislative Activity: Records of Congressmen, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - McCarren Bill, 1952 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - McCarren Act, Undated (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - McKellar Bill and Resolution, 1943 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Mundt-Nixon Bill, 1948-1949 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Mundt-Nixon Bill, 1949 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Mundt Bill, 1950 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Mundt Bill: Correspondence, 1948 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Opposition to Mundt Bill: Correspondence, 1948 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Signatures Against Mundt Bill, 1948 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Report Violations of Free Speech and Rights of Labor, Undated (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - New York State Legislative Practices Committee, 1961 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - New York State Legislation, 1956 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Ober Bill (Maryland), 1950 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Passports Legislation, 1951-1958 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Poverty Legislation, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Price Control Legislation, 1944-1945 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Public Defender Bill (Albany), 1950 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Public Defender, 1953-1955 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Reconversion Bill, 1944 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Second Class Mailing Privileges Bill, 1954 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Legislation: Security Risk, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Senate Bill No. 27, 1960 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Services Vote Legislation, 1944 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Social Legislation, 1940-1948 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Social Legislation, 1948 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Social Legislation: Health, 1945-1949 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Social Legislation: Health, 1947-1949 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Social Legislation: Housing, 1936, 1939, 1940 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Social Legislation: Housing, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Social Legislation: Taxation, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Social Legislation: Taxation, Undated (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Social Legislation: Unemployment Insurance, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Social Legislation: WMO Health Act of 1945 [I], 1945-1946 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Social Legislation: WMO Health Act of 1945 [II], 1945-1946 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Social Welfare, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Social Security Legislation: Correspondence, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - State Legislative Committee, 1955 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Statements/Reports Legislative, 1957-1959 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Analysis of Taft Hartley Bill, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Taft-Hartley Act, 1948 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - US Constitution Amendments "Court of the Union", 1963 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Wagner-Morse Case Anti-Lynching Bill, 1948 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Walter Omnibus Bill, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 31)
- Part 1, Series XII: Cases: General Files, 1934-1967
  - Abercrombie Enterprises v. Edward Opton, North Carolina, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Adler et al. v. NYS Dept. of Education, Undated (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - James E. Allen v. Board of Education, 1959 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - American Communications Association, Selly v. Douds, 1949 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Amicus Briefs (misc.), 1949-1952 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Parker J. Andrews, 1949 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Anastaplo, George [I], 1954 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Anastaplo, George [II], 1954 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Anastaplo, George, 1957 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Anastaplo, George [I], 1959 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Anastaplo, George [II], 1959 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Apalachin Gang, 1960 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Apostoloff v. Apostoloff, 1941 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Application for Elimination or Modification of Interrogatories, 1954 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Attorney General v. NLG, 1950-1959 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Aurelio, 1943 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Bailey v. Richards, 1950 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Baker v. Baker, 1951 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Baltimore Smith Act Case, 1953 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Barenblatt v. US, 1958 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Barenblatt, 1959 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Barsky, 1947-1948 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Barsky v. US, Undated (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Baton Rouge Omnibus Suit (SNCC), 1962 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Sylvester Billik, Deceased, 1917-1952 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Benemovsky v. Sullivan, 1948 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Birmingham Case, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - Bjornson, 1953 (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - Mabel Black v. Cutter Laboratories, 1954 (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Bondy Distributors Inc., 1952 (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Borges v. Yew, 1950 (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - Braden, 1956-1957 (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - Maurice Louis Braverman [I], 1951-1956 (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - Maurice Louis Braverman [II], 1951-1956 (Box 35, Folder 34)
  - Braverman Re: Smith Act, 1952 (Box 35, Folder 35)
  - Harry Bridges Deportation, 1942 (Box 35, Folder 36)
  - Harry Bridges, 1945 (Box 35, Folder 37)
  - Harry Bridges v. US, 1949 (Box 35, Folder 38)
  - Briefs: Anti Kansas Law Restriction Labor Rights, Undated (Box 35, Folder 39)
  - Brief of the Proposed Designation of the National Lawyers Guild, 1956 (Box 35, Folder 40)
  - Briggs v. Elliott, 1952 (Box 35, Folder 41)
  - Brown v. Board of Education, 1953-1955 (Box 35, Folder 42)
  - Bufalino v. US, 1960 (Box 35, Folder 43)
  - Burko, 1951 (Box 35, Folder 44)
  - Philip B. Burns, 1949 (Box 35, Folder 45)
  - Burstyn v. Wilson, 1952 (Box 35, Folder 46)
  - California v. Dorado, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Harold I. Cammer v. US, 1954 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Study on the Right to Council, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Isaiah Cash, 1953 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - John Caughlan, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Cherner, 1952 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Jules Chopak, 1946 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - CIO v. Harry B. Mitchell, 1945 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Court Clerks: Attorneys Replies, 1956 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Cobb v. Montgomery, Alabama, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Cocchi and Fruciante v. Grande and Grande, 1936 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Albert Martin Cohen, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Albert Martin Cohen v. Denis M. Hurley, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Cohen v. Hurley [I], 1960 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Cohen v. Hurley [II], 1960 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Simon Cohen v. Board of Transportation, 1950 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Coleman v. Aycock, 1967 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Columbia Pictures: NLRB (Amicus Brief), 1945 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Communist Party of the US v. J. Howard McGrath, 1951-1953 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Communist Party of the US v. Subversive Activities Control Board, 1955 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - George Condulis, 1951 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Conference of Chief Justices, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Constitutional Liberties Case: FBI, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Constitutional Liberties Albertson and Proctor v. SACB, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Continental Motors Corp., 1939-1940 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - NLG Case for Prosecution of "Social Justice" and Charles E. Coughlin, 1942 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Court of Public Opinion: People of the US v. the Dies Committee, 1939 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Daneville, VA Omnibus Suit, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - District of Columbia v. John R. Thompson Co. Inc., 1949 (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - Appeal: District of Columbia v. John R. Thompson Co. Inc., 1949 (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - Domestic Relations:Cases, 1961 (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - DuBois Club, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - Eisler Case, 1947 (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - Eisler v. US, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 34)
  - Eisler v. US, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 35)
  - Elfbrandt Case: Arizona Loyalty Oath Case, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 36)
  - Harry Ellman, 1941 (Box 36, Folder 37)
  - Eugene v. Mandel, 1949 (Box 36, Folder 38)
  - Falcone Brothers, 1956 (Box 36, Folder 39)
  - Rose Fertig, 1951 (Box 36, Folder 40)
  - Fishermen v. US (Supreme Court Re: Employment of Communists), 1950 (Box 36, Folder 41)
  - Mitchell Franklin, 1956-1957 (Box 36, Folder 42)
  - Morton Freidman v. Lewis B. Swellenbach, 1946 (Box 36, Folder 43)
  - Thelma Furry, 1955 (Box 36, Folder 44)
  - US v. Elizabeth Gurley Flynn, et al., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 45)
  - US v. Elizabeth Gurley Flynn, et al., 1951 (Box 36, Folder 46)
  - US v. Elizabeth Gurley Flynn, et al., Undated (Box 36, Folder 47)
  - Four Continent Book Corp., 1949 (Box 36, Folder 48)
  - Laurent Frantz, 1949 (Box 36, Folder 49)
  - Gadsen Omnibus Suit, 1962 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Gainsville Case, 1944 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Melvin and Helen Gaulden, 1951 (Box 37, Folder 3)